(This program is intended for mature audiences. It may feature explicit content, violence, and strong language)
(이 프로그램은 성인 시청자를 대상으로 합니다. 노골적인 내용, 폭력, 거친 언어가 포함될 수 있습니다)
(All characters, places, and events in this series are entirely fictitious)
(모든 캐릭터, 장소, 이벤트 이 시리즈의 내용은 완전히 허구입니다.)
Why your hair was longer
머리가 더 길어진 이유
in the ID? It's short now.
아이디에? 이제 짧습니다.
- Hey, bro. - Come in.
- 안녕, 형. - 들어오세요.
Look, the cops are here.
보세요, 경찰이 여기 있어요.
- Make sure everything's put away. - Hello, bro. Hold on.
- 모든 것이 정리되었는지 확인하세요. - 안녕, 형. 기다리다.
Show me your ID.
신분증을 보여주세요.
Check your ID.
신분증을 확인하세요.
You're here, right?
여기 계시죠?
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
Excuse me. May I...
실례합니다. 내가...
Hey, buddy.
안녕, 친구.
Are you of age?
당신은 나이가 있습니까?
Yes, I am.
네, 그렇습니다.
Hey, open the door.
이봐, 문 좀 열어봐.
Hey! The cops are here.
여기요! 경찰이 여기 있어요.
Show me your ID...
신분증을 보여주세요...
It's on the table.
테이블 위에 있어요.
Hey! What are you doing?
여기요! 뭐하세요?
Hey! Show me your ID.
여기요! 신분증을 보여주세요.
Hey! Stay right there!
여기요! 거기 그대로 있어!
Everyone, stay calm!
다들 침착하세요!
Right at the table!
바로 테이블!
Don't move!
움직이지 마세요!
You're under arrest
당신은 체포되었습니다
for stealing my heart.
내 마음을 훔쳤기 때문에.
Wow.
우와.
Watching youngsters dance like this, anyone catch your eye?
젊은이들이 이렇게 춤추는 걸 보면 눈에 띄는 사람 있어?
Not sure yet.
아직 확실하지 않습니다.
Stay a little longer. You'll find your favorite soon.
조금 더 머물다 가세요. 곧 마음에 드는 것을 찾을 수 있을 것입니다.
We are at your service.
우리는 귀하의 서비스를 제공합니다.
Oh! Thank you.
오! 감사합니다.
That one over there is pretty great.
저기 있는 그거 꽤 훌륭해요.
A perfect ten. No notes!
완벽한 10개. 메모가 없습니다!
Get ready. The VIP clients are coming.
준비하세요. VIP 고객이 찾아옵니다.
Hello, Mr. Chain.
안녕하세요, 체인씨.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Was there much traffic today?
오늘 교통량이 많았나요?
Not really.
설마.
Looking good as always.
언제나처럼 좋아 보이네요.
I've got the VIP spot ready for you. This way, please.
당신을 위한 VIP 자리를 준비했습니다. 이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Is this him?
이 사람인가요?
The rookie. The second-best in this place.
신인. 이 곳에서 두 번째로 좋은 곳입니다.
Yes. Fresh, lively, and charming.
예. 신선하고 활기차고 매력적입니다.
Then I'm booking him for the night.
그럼 내가 그 사람에게 밤을 보내도록 예약할게.
Chain.
체인.
Should I take your bag and put it away for you?
네 가방을 가져갈까? 그리고 당신을 위해 그것을 치워두었나요?
No, it's fine.
아니요, 괜찮아요.
I'll handle it.
제가 처리하겠습니다.
Please, go ahead.
계속하세요.
Everything's ready for you.
모든 것이 준비되어 있습니다.
Thanks for keeping me company today.
오늘 나와 함께 있어줘서 고마워요.
My pleasure.
천만에요.
The weather is so nice. Do you want to shower first?
날씨가 너무 좋아요. 먼저 샤워할래?
You go ahead, Chain.
어서 가세요, 체인.
If we go in together, it'll spoil the surprise.
같이 들어가면 그것은 놀라움을 망칠 것입니다.
It won't be gone. The surprise thing.
그것은 사라지지 않을 것입니다. 놀라운 점.
Fine.
괜찮은.
Oh, my!
아, 이런!
Tonight, you'll get to try everything.
오늘 밤, 당신은 모든 것을 시도하게 될 것입니다.
Chain,
체인,
there's nothing like, "boyfriend-like" style? You know, cute and sweet and stuff?
남친같은 스타일은 없나요? 귀엽고 다정한 것 아시죠?
Like cat ears or maybe a blindfold?
고양이 귀나 눈가리개 같은 거요?
No cat ears today.
오늘은 고양이 귀가 없습니다.
Only cat tails.
고양이 꼬리만 있습니다.
I was told it will just be
그냥 그렇게 될 거라고 들었어
boyfriend vibes.
남자친구 분위기.
Yeah. It's a boyfriend vibe with toys.
응. 장난감을 가지고 있는 남자친구 분위기예요.
Now, I'm starting to feel it.
이제 나는 그것을 느끼기 시작했습니다.
Let's get started then.
그럼 시작해 보겠습니다.
Hey! Chain!
여기요! 체인!
Hey! Wait a second.
여기요! 잠깐만요.
Hold on.
기다리다.
Chain, I only do entertainment jobs.
체인 씨, 저는 연예계 일만 해요.
I already told Sky.
나는 이미 스카이에게 말했다.
I asked for an extreme service.
파격적인 서비스를 요청했어요.
(Mom: Don't forget to transfer the money. 40,000 baht)
(엄마: 잊지 마세요 돈을 이체하기 위해. 40,000바트)
(Enter your PIN, Balance: 15,250.48 baht)
(PIN을 입력하세요. 잔액: 15,250.48바트)
Tai.
타이.
Huh?
뭐?
I don't think I'm renewing my gym membership this month.
갱신은 안 하는 것 같아요 이번달 내 체육관 회원권이야.
Hey. I can cover you for this month if you want.
여기요. 난 널 덮을 수 있어 원한다면 이번 달 동안.
No, it's fine.
아니요, 괜찮아요.
My expenses are just piling up.
지출이 쌓여가고 있어요.
I figured if I just cut back on the gym, I'd be okay.
그냥 줄이면 어떨까 생각했는데 체육관에서는 괜찮을 것 같아요.
It's called investment, man.
그걸 투자라고 해요.
If you get that great physique,
그 정도로 몸매가 좋다면
you might start bringing in a lot more cash.
당신은 가져 오기 시작할 수도 있습니다 현금이 훨씬 더 많습니다.
Yeah, I know.
응, 알아요.
But I'm just struggling with my cash flow right now.
하지만 난 그냥 힘들어 지금 내 현금 흐름.
Interested in some side gigs?
부업 공연에 관심이 있으신가요?
Entertain jobs, boyfriend vibes. Stuff like that. The pay is insane.
즐거운 일, 남자친구 분위기. 그런 것. 급여가 미쳤네요.
Nosy guy.
코가 많은 사람.
No, thanks. I wouldn't feel comfortable doing that.
아니요, 고마워요. 나는 느끼지 않을 것이다 그렇게 하면 편해요.
Come on! It's easy money.
어서 해봐요! 돈은 쉽습니다.
If you don't want to 'sell', just do the entertainment part for fun.
'판매'를 원하지 않는다면, 그냥 재미로 오락적인 부분을 하세요.
Look, I'm swamped with clients right now.
보세요, 저는 지금 고객들로 꽉 차 있어요.
If you're interested, I'll share some with you.
관심이 있으시면, 몇 가지를 여러분과 공유하겠습니다.
I have a client looking for a "cute" type right now.
찾는 고객이 있어요 지금은 "귀엽다"는 타입.
Here's a quick briefing.
간단한 브리핑은 이렇습니다.
This is Mr. Chain.
체인 씨입니다.
He's one of our regulars.
그 사람은 우리 단골 중 한 명이에요.
He likes the "boyfriend" vibe.
그는 '남자친구' 분위기를 좋아한다.
Likes to play with a few little toys, like blindfolds and cat ears, stuff like that.
작은 장난감 몇 개 가지고 노는 걸 좋아하고, 눈가리개나 고양이 귀 같은 것 말이죠.
Don't worry. He doesn't do drugs.
괜찮아요. 그는 마약을 하지 않습니다.
I never take jobs like that.
나는 결코 그런 직업을 갖지 않습니다.
I don't want to ruin my reputation.
나는 내 평판을 망치고 싶지 않습니다.
It's just like working at the club.
클럽에서 일하는 것과 똑같습니다.
Just entertain, right?
그냥 즐겁게 지내세요, 그렇죠?
Exactly.
정확히.
Chain, I want to cancel this job.
체인 씨, 이 일을 취소하고 싶어요.
This isn't what we agreed on.
이것은 우리가 합의한 것이 아닙니다.
I'm really sorry.
정말 죄송해요.
You have no right to boss me around.
당신은 나를 상사로 삼을 권리가 없습니다.
Okay. Fine.
좋아요. 괜찮은.
That's more like it.
그게 더 비슷해요.
Make it worth the money I've wasted.
내가 낭비한 돈만큼 가치 있게 만들어 보세요.
From now on, you're my slave.
이제부터 넌 내 노예야.
Done for.
완료되었습니다.
Help!
돕다!
Someone help me!
누군가 나를 도와주세요!
Come here!
이리 오세요!
You're into this and you never told me.
당신은 이것에 관심이 있고 나에게 말한 적이 없습니다.
How did police get in here?
경찰이 여기 어떻게 들어왔나요?
Sir!
선생님!
Hey!
여기요!
Let me go!
날 보내줘!
Let go of me! Let go!
날 놔줘! 가자!
Hey!
여기요!
Sir!
선생님!
Heaven...
천국...
Are there cops in heaven too?
천국에도 경찰이 있나요?
What exactly are you arresting me for?
나를 체포하려는 이유가 정확히 무엇입니까?
Where is your evidence?
당신의 증거는 어디에 있습니까?
Calm down, sir.
진정하세요.
What's case?
어떤 경우인가요?
It's the Soi 2 case.
소이2 사건입니다.
How can I stay calm? Show me the evidence!
어떻게 침착함을 유지할 수 있나요? 증거를 보여주세요!
Please come with me, Chainphop.
저와 함께 가주세요, 체인팝.
(Police Captain, Deputy Investigation Inspector, Kritsadawut Siriwatmontri)
(경찰서장, 수사부감찰관, 크리차다우트 시리와트몬트리)
Police Captain Kritsadawut.
경찰 대장 Kritsadawut.
Tell me what I did wrong!
내가 뭘 잘못했는지 말해주세요!
There are several counts, actually.
실제로는 여러 가지가 있습니다.
But assault is the primary charge.
그러나 폭행이 주요 혐의입니다.
I told you, it was an accident!
내가 말했잖아, 그건 사고였어!
I could actually sue you
실제로 당신을 고소할 수도 있어요
for trespassing without a warrant!
영장 없이 무단 침입하다니!
It took everything I had
내가 가진 모든 것을 다 가져가버렸어
just to bring you in for questioning.
당신을 데려와서 심문하려고요.
I'm certainly not letting you go easily.
나는 확실히 당신을 쉽게 보내지 않을 것입니다.
Sergeant!
중사!
Sergeant! Take that one in the room too.
중사! 그것도 방에 가져가세요.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Let go of me!
날 놔줘!
(Two weeks ago)
(2주 전)
Thank you, Sir.
감사합니다.
(Police Major General, Investigation Inspector, Athip Phongwilai)
(경찰 소장, 수사관, Athip Phongwilai)
Krit.
크릿.
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
(Chainphop Udomdirek, 32)
(Chainphop Udomdirek, 32)
I want you to handle this case.
당신이 이 사건을 처리해줬으면 좋겠어요.
The previous team failed to take him down.
이전 팀은 그를 쓰러뜨리지 못했습니다.
Chain has powerful connections.
체인에는 강력한 연결이 있습니다.
Understood.
이해했다.
I'll shadow his every move and find the evidence to catch him red-handed.
나는 그의 모든 움직임을 따라갈 것이다 그를 적발할 증거를 찾으세요.
Good.
좋은.
If you run into any trouble or need anything else, let me know.
어떤 문제에 부딪히면 아니면 다른 것이 필요하면 알려주세요.
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
One more thing.
한 가지 더.
If you close this case, I'm sure your dad will be very proud of you.
만약 당신이 이 사건을 종결한다면, 난 확신해요 네 아버지는 너를 매우 자랑스러워하실 거야.
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
(Suspect in a drug-related case, Chainphop Udomdirek, 32, Owner of C Group Logistic export business)
(마약 관련 사건의 피의자 Chainphop Udomdirek, 32, C그룹 물류수출사업주)
(Get ready. The VIP clients are coming.)
(준비하세요. VIP 고객님들이 오십니다.)
Hello, Mr. Chain.
안녕하세요, 체인씨.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Was there much traffic today?
오늘 교통량이 많았나요?
Not really.
설마.
Looking good as always.
언제나처럼 좋아 보이네요.
You seem to visit this hotel quite often.
이 호텔을 꽤 자주 방문하시는 것 같아요.
My friend owns shares in the hotel.
내 친구가 호텔 주식을 소유하고 있어요.
I'm just trying to support a friend.
나는 단지 친구를 지원하려고 노력하고 있습니다.
Must be a very good friend.
아주 좋은 친구임에 틀림없어요.
According to CCTV footage,
CCTV 영상에 따르면,
you've entered and exited this hotel dozens of times in the past month.
당신은 이 호텔에 들어오고 나갔습니다 지난 한 달 동안 수십 번.
And always with a different person.
그리고 항상 다른 사람과 함께.
What? Are the cops getting into other people's love lives now too?
무엇? 경찰이 들어가고 있는 걸까 다른 사람의 러브라이브도 지금도 살고 있나요?
Usually, we don't. Not unless there's something suspicious.
일반적으로 우리는 그렇지 않습니다. 뭔가 의심스러운 게 없다면 말이죠.
Evidence shows money being transferred into your friend's personal account.
돈이 이체되고 있다는 증거가 있습니다 친구의 개인 계정으로.
Millions at a time.
한 번에 수백만 달러.
A hotel room shouldn't cost millions, should it?
호텔 방 수백만 달러의 비용이 들지 않아야합니까?
Maybe it was a mistake.
어쩌면 실수였을 수도 있습니다.
I can just have my friend send it back.
친구에게 다시 보내달라고 하면 됩니다.
Besides, I'm not exactly hurting for money.
게다가 난 꼭 그렇지도 않아 돈 때문에 아프다.
Giving more to a friend doesn't bother me.
친구에게 더 많이 주는 것은 나를 괴롭히지 않습니다.
If that's all, call me next time, Officer.
그게 다라면 다음에 전화해주세요, 경관님.
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
Wait.
기다리다.
I haven't finished the interrogation.
심문이 끝나지 않았습니다.
So, what happened this time?
그렇다면 이번에는 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
It's not hard to guess, is it?
추측하기 어렵지 않죠?
It was just bedroom talk.
그냥 침실 이야기였어요.
That's not true, Officer! It wasn't just that!
그건 사실이 아닙니다, 경관님! 그것만이 아니었습니다!
Tell me what happened.
무슨 일이 일어났는지 말해주세요.
Yes, Sir.
네, 선생님.
He assaulted me!
그 사람이 나를 폭행했어요!
It was an accident.
그것은 사고였습니다.
That's a lie, Officer!
그건 거짓말이에요, 경관님!
I was trying to escape.
나는 탈출하려고했다.
He tried to force himself on me with some weird toys.
그 사람이 나한테 강요하려고 했어 이상한 장난감과 함께.
Officer, you know? Such a huge thing!
경관님, 아시죠? 정말 엄청난 일이에요!
And some cat tail thing, and handcuffs.
그리고 고양이 꼬리랑 수갑도요.
Those aren't mine.
그건 내 것이 아닙니다.
Liar!
거짓말쟁이!
Here's the thing. He's not my boyfriend.
여기에 문제가 있습니다. 그 사람은 내 남자친구가 아니거든요.
Then what is your relationship?
그렇다면 당신의 관계는 무엇입니까?
Based on the evidence, this looks like a solicitation case.
증거를 바탕으로, 이건 청탁 사건인 것 같아요.
If I can't charge you with anything else,
다른 비용을 청구할 수 없다면
I can start by arresting you both for prostitution.
너희 둘 다 체포하는 것부터 시작하면 돼 매춘을 위해.
Wait! I'm not finished yet.
기다리다! 아직 끝나지 않았습니다.
He's not my boyfriend.
그 사람은 내 남자친구가 아니거든요.
But...
하지만...
He's my ex-boyfriend.
그 사람은 내 전 남자친구예요.
We were having a fight.
우리는 싸우고있었습니다.
We were trying something new in bed,
우리는 침대에서 새로운 것을 시도하고 있었어요
but I got scared it would hurt.
하지만 아플까 봐 무서웠어요.
But he wouldn't stop. He was toxic and forced himself on me.
그러나 그는 멈추지 않았습니다. 그는 독성이 있었고 나에게 강요했습니다.
You're an open-minded boyfriend.
당신은 개방적인 남자 친구입니다.
Letting your partner sleep with someone new every night.
파트너와 함께 자게 놔두기 매일 밤 새로운 사람.
Is this some kind of open relationship?
이것은 일종의 개방적인 관계입니까?
Well, I actually just found out about that, Officer.
글쎄요, 사실 방금 알아냈어요 그것에 대해요, 경관님.
I guess we really should break up for good now, Officer.
내 생각엔 우리가 정말 그래야 할 것 같아 이제 완전히 헤어지세요, 경관님.
Fine. It's over.
괜찮은. 끝났습니다.
Fine by me.
난 괜찮아.
(Central Investigation Department) Once all the fees are paid, we're done here, right?
(중앙수사부) 비용을 모두 지불하면 이제 끝이겠죠?
Fine by me.
난 괜찮아.
Wait.
기다리다.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Let me tend to your wound first.
먼저 당신의 상처를 치료해 드리겠습니다.
This might sting a bit.
이건 좀 따가울 수도 있어요.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
Does it hurt?
아프나요?
Oh.
오.
No.
아니요.
It's just that...
그게 바로 그거야...
You're not like other cops.
당신은 다른 경찰과 다릅니다.
And you...
그리고 당신은...
You don't look much like a cop either.
당신도 경찰처럼 보이지 않네요.
So,
그래서,
don't ever dress up as a police officer again.
절대로 옷을 입지 마세요 다시 경찰로.
You saw that?
그거 봤어?
It was an entertaining show.
재미있는 쇼였습니다.
But really...
하지만 정말...
You're better off not wearing that uniform again.
넌 안 하는 게 낫지 그 유니폼을 다시 입는다.
I see.
알겠어요.
Finished?
완성된?
Yes.
예.
But there's one thing I want to tell you.
그런데 한 가지 말씀드리고 싶은 것이 있습니다.
You only got away with it today
오늘에서야 무사히 끝났어
because you're a smooth talker.
당신은 말을 잘하는 사람이니까.
But you weren't exactly convincing.
하지만 당신은 별로 설득력이 없었어요.
I'm saying this now, just in case there's a next time.
내가 지금 이 말을 하는 것은, 혹시 다음 번에 있을 경우를 대비해.
Because if it had been any other officer,
다른 장교였다면
they would have arrested you already.
그들은 이미 당신을 체포했을 것입니다.
What are you talking about, Officer?
무슨 말을 하는 겁니까, 경관님?
I have no idea what you mean.
무슨 말인지 모르겠어요.
But
하지만
thank you
감사합니다
for the lesson.
수업을 위해.
And I really am hurt, you know. I'm not acting.
그리고 난 정말 상처받았어요. 나는 연기하지 않습니다.
I believe you.
나는 당신을 믿습니다.
With a wound like that,
그런 상처가 있어서
you should really go to a hospital.
너 진짜 병원에 가봐야 해.
I'll be fine.
나는 괜찮을 것이다.
Anyway, thank you so much.
어쨌든 정말 고마워요.
I'll be going now.
나는 지금 갈 것이다.
Right.
오른쪽.
What?
무엇?
Officer.
장교.
I was really shocked just now.
나 지금 정말 충격받았어.
I just realized that
방금 깨달았어
on my way back,
돌아오는 길에
I might get attacked by my ex-boyfriend.
전 남자친구한테 공격받을 수도 있어요.
Oh, dear.
이런.
This is just terrible.
정말 끔찍해요.
Ah.
아.
So, Officer, could you give me a ride home?
그러니까, 경관님, 집까지 태워다 주실 수 있나요?
(Thai police are dedicated to public safety)
(태국 경찰은 전담 공공 안전을 위해)
"Thai police are dedicated to public safety."
"태국 경찰은 헌신적이다 공공 안전을 위해."
Right?
오른쪽?
(Just Being the Last One Whom You Think Of)
(그저 마지막 사람이 되는 것 뿐이야 당신이 생각하는 사람)
♪Standing where I never should have been♪
♪내가 절대로 있어서는 안 될 곳에 서 있었어♪
♪And honestly, that's enough for me♪
♪그리고 솔직히 저는 그것만으로도 충분해요♪
Why do you do this work?
왜 이 일을 하는가?
What work do you mean?
무슨 일을 하라는 겁니까?
You can stop acting now.
이제 행동을 멈춰도 됩니다.
Tell me.
말해 주세요.
Nothing you say here will be used as evidence.
여기서는 아무 말도 안 해 증거로 활용됩니다.
Well...
음...
Truth is, I'm a bar host.
사실 저는 바 호스트입니다.
Just came to take an "entertain" job outside today.
그냥 데리러 왔어 오늘은 밖에서 "즐거운" 일을 하세요.
First time.
처음으로.
And as you saw,
그리고 보시다시피,
I ran straight into that guy.
나는 바로 그 사람에게 달려갔다.
Oh, Officer.
아, 경관님.
I'm not a "boy for sale" or anything. Don't misunderstand.
나는 "판매용 소년"이나 그 어떤 것도 아닙니다. 오해하지 마세요.
I'm not looking down on your profession.
나는 당신의 직업을 무시하지 않습니다.
I'm just curious. Is there a difference?
그냥 궁금해서요. 차이점이 있나요?
♪Even if there's no one else up there♪
♪위에 아무도 없더라도♪
♪I know full well♪
♪잘 알고 있어요♪
♪It's still not me♪
♪아직 내가 아니야♪
Well...
음...
There is.
있습니다.
Usually, there's a big difference.
일반적으로 큰 차이가 있습니다.
It's just...
그냥...
This time I took it as a side gig.
이번에는 사이드 공연으로 잡았습니다.
The reason is pretty common. I just needed the money.
그 이유는 매우 일반적입니다. 그냥 돈이 필요했어요.
♪Just being the last one whom you look at♪
♪마지막으로 보는 사람이 되는 것뿐♪
So,
그래서,
how did you find me today anyway?
그나저나 오늘 나를 어떻게 찾았어요?
It's classified information.
기밀 정보입니다.
♪More than I dreamed of♪
♪내가 꿈꾸던 것보다 더 많은 것♪
Oh.
오.
And why did you become a cop?
그리고 왜 경찰이 되었나요?
Nothing special.
특별한 것은 없습니다.
♪Someone is standing there♪
♪누군가 거기 서 있어요♪
♪Right there up in your stars♪
♪바로 저기 당신의 별에♪
♪Even if there's no one else up there♪
♪위에 아무도 없더라도♪
♪I know full well♪
♪잘 알고 있어요♪
♪It's still not me♪
♪아직 내가 아니야♪
♪Just being the last one♪
♪마지막이 되는 것 뿐이야♪
Um, Officer? Could I ask for one more favor?
음, 경관님? 하나만 더 부탁드려도 될까요?
♪Standing where I never should have been♪
♪내가 절대로 있어서는 안 될 곳에 서 있었어♪
Could you roll down the window? I'm feeling dizzy.
창문을 내려 주시겠어요? 현기증이 나네요.
♪Just being the last one whom you look at♪
♪마지막으로 보는 사람이 되는 것뿐♪
♪To be in your cold gaze♪
♪차가운 시선 속에 있기를♪
♪Just being here, beneath the stars♪
♪별빛 아래 여기 있는 것만으로도♪
♪I'm so happy♪
♪정말 기뻐요♪
You okay?
괜찮아?
Much better. Thanks.
훨씬 나아졌습니다. 감사해요.
Thank you so much, Officer.
정말 감사합니다, 경관님.
Sorry, but can I bother you one last time? Can I borrow your phone? I need to call my mom.
미안하지만 마지막으로 귀찮게 해도 될까요? 전화기를 빌려도 될까요? 엄마에게 전화해야 해요.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Hey! Don't call yet! I'm in the middle of a Live Sale!
여기요! 아직 전화하지 마세요! 라이브 세일 중이에요!
How do I hang this up?
이걸 어떻게 끊나요?
- Oh. - Mom!
- 오. - 엄마!
Where's Singto?
싱토는 어디 있지?
He's sleeping in the house.
그는 집에서 자고 있습니다.
Oh, my!
아, 이런!
I missed it!
나는 그것을 놓쳤다!
Mom! Why did you leave Singto alone?
엄마! 왜 싱토를 내버려두셨나요?
How can know I where you are?
당신이 어디에 있는지 어떻게 알 수 있나요?
I was hungry, so I went out to eat!
배가 고파서 먹으러 나갔어요!
Here!
여기!
Do you know who I'm with? This is a police officer!
내가 누구랑 같이 있는지 아세요? 이 사람은 경찰이에요!
I'll have him arrest you!
그 사람이 당신을 체포하도록 할게요!
Ugh!
윽!
What is Singto doing?
싱토는 뭐하고 있어요?
I'm so sorry about that.
정말 미안해요.
Thanks again.
다시 한 번 감사드립니다.
And sorry again.
그리고 다시 한 번 죄송합니다.
You had to see us bickering
우리가 말다툼하는 걸 봤어야 했어
on such a tiring day.
이렇게 피곤한 날에.
I'm used to seeing it.
나는 그것을 보는 데 익숙합니다.
Right.
오른쪽.
Well...
음...
It was nice meeting you, Officer.
만나서 반가웠습니다, 경관님.
I hope
그러길 바라요
we have the chance to meet again.
우리는 다시 만날 기회가 있어요.
Nice to meet you, too.
저도 만나서 반가워요.
But next time we meet,
하지만 다음에 만나면
I hope it's not as an officer and a suspect.
아니길 바라요 장교이자 용의자로서.
If you really don't want to get arrested,
정말 체포되고 싶지 않다면
stay away from the illegal trade, okay?
불법거래는 멀리하세요, 알았죠?
I will.
그럴게요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Go inside.
안으로 들어가세요.
There, there.
저기, 저기.
Don't cry.
울지 마세요.
Did you transfer it yet?
아직 전송하셨나요?
Not yet, Mom.
아직은 아니에요, 엄마.
Mom.
엄마.
You have to promise me.
나한테 약속해야 해.
You'll save it. If you don't, no matter how much I give you, it'll never be enough.
저장하면 됩니다. 그렇지 않다면 상관없어요 내가 당신에게 얼마나 주는지 결코 충분하지 않을 것입니다.
I am saving!
나는 저축하고있다!
Otherwise, how would I have money to get into a share savings scheme?
그렇지 않으면 어떻게 돈을 벌 수 있겠습니까? 주식 저축 계획에 참여하려면?
Then how did you end up in so much debt?
그러면 어떻게 해서 그렇게 많은 빚을지게 되었습니까?
Mom.
엄마.
Ugh!
윽!
- I'm hot. I'm going to take a shower! - Mom, I'm tired of saying this.
- 더워요. 나는 샤워를 할 것이다! - 엄마, 이런 말을 하기가 지겨워요.
- Let's go to sleep. - Mom.
- 자러 가자. - 엄마.
Okay, let's go to sleep.
알았어, 자러 가자.
I'll transfer the 40,000 baht to you.
40,000바트를 당신에게 양도하겠습니다.
See? You can earn money if you really try.
보다? 정말 노력하면 돈을 벌 수 있습니다.
Mom.
엄마.
In this industry,
이 업계에서는
I don't even know how much longer I can keep earning like this.
얼마나 더 남았는지도 모르겠어 계속 이렇게 벌 수 있어요.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
I watched a clip the other day.
저번에 클립을 봤어요.
It said that
It said that
don't be afraid of being embarrassed.
부끄러워하는 것을 두려워하지 마십시오.
People aren't born equal.
사람은 평등하게 태어나지 않습니다.
We are not all born with the same advantages.
우리는 모두 태어난 것이 아니다 동일한 장점을 가지고 있습니다.
You were born handsome.
당신은 잘생겼어요.
You have to use that to your advantage. Why bother with architecture?
그것을 유리하게 활용해야 합니다. 왜 건축에 신경을 쓰나요?
Staying up all night, who knows if you'll even make this much when you graduate?
밤새도록 깨어있어, 네가 그럴지 누가 알겠어? 졸업하면 이만큼 벌어?
I'm fine with it.
난 괜찮아요.
Hmm?
흠?
Oh, Mom.
아, 엄마.
I don't care what people think or if they gossip about me.
사람들이 어떻게 생각하든 상관없어 아니면 그들이 나에 대해 험담을 한다면.
I'm just worried about when my liver is going to give out.
그냥 걱정돼 내 간이 망가질 때.
Mom.
엄마.
I'm serious.
나는 진지하다.
You really need to start saving.
정말로 저축을 시작해야 합니다.
Besides, Singto still isn't talking yet.
게다가 싱토는 아직 말을 하지 않고 있어요.
We have to take him to see a doctor.
그를 의사에게 데려가야 해요.
Yeah.
응.
I get it.
알겠습니다.
Just buy a frog to hit its mouth. No need to see a doctor. Saves us a lot of money.
그냥 입에 맞도록 개구리를 사세요. 의사를 만날 필요가 없습니다. 우리에게 많은 돈을 절약해 줍니다.
Oh, Mom!
아, 엄마!
That's your grandson. Don't you worry about him at all?
그 사람은 당신의 손자입니다. 그 사람에 대해서는 전혀 걱정하지 않나요?
Well, tell Wai to pay for it herself then.
그럼 Wai에게 직접 비용을 지불하라고 하세요.
He's her kid.
그는 그녀의 아이입니다.
You reap what you sow.
당신은 당신이 뿌린대로 거둔다.
My money is my money.
내 돈은 내 돈이다.
Time to take the righteous path, right, Mom?
의로운 길을 택할 시간, 그렇지, 엄마?
Sky, you bad guy!
스카이, 나쁜 놈아!
Why didn't you tell me everything?
왜 나에게 모든 것을 말하지 않았나요?
What? I've told you everything.
무엇? 나는 당신에게 모든 것을 말했습니다.
Everything?
모든 것?
That guy wanted an extreme service. Why didn't you mention it?
그 사람은 극단적인 서비스를 원했어요. 왜 언급하지 않았나요?
I told you what I heard.
나는 내가 들은 것을 당신에게 말했다.
What now?
지금은 무엇입니까?
You don't even look sorry.
당신은 미안해 보이지도 않습니다.
Wayu's head got busted because of your weird client.
와유 머리가 터졌네 이상한 고객 때문에요.
Hey!
여기요!
How was I supposed to know?
내가 어떻게 알겠어요?
- You didn't know? - Hey!
- 몰랐어요? - 여기요!
- That was your regular client.
- 단골손님이셨어요.
Normally, you're stingy. Why did you share all of a sudden?
평소에는 인색해요. 갑자기 왜 공유한 걸까요?
- Stop it! - Tai.
- 그만해요! - 타이.
- Did you set him up on purpose? - Tai, calm down.
- 일부러 그 사람을 설정한 건가요? - 타이, 진정해요.
Just calm down.
진정하세요.
It's not worth getting into trouble.
문제를 일으킬 가치가 없습니다.
Hold on.
기다리다.
Fine.
괜찮은.
Think whatever you want.
원하는대로 생각하십시오.
I even shared my client with you.
나는 심지어 내 고객을 당신과 공유했습니다.
Darn it!
젠장!
Kids these days.
요즘 애들.
They have no idea what "gratitude" means.
그들은 "감사"가 무엇을 의미하는지 전혀 모릅니다.
You're right, Sky.
네 말이 맞아, 스카이.
Oh.
오.
I get it now.
이제 알겠습니다.
The reason you got your head busted
머리가 터진 이유
wasn't because of the client.
클라이언트 때문이 아니었습니다.
It's because you are bad at your job.
그건 당신이 일을 잘 못하기 때문이에요.
Sky, you wretch!
스카이, 이 가엾은 놈아!
- What? - Hey!
- 무엇? - 여기요!
Oh, my! Not the face!
아, 이런! 얼굴이 아니야!
- My face cost a fortune! - Bring it on!
- 내 얼굴에 엄청난 돈이 들었어! - 가져와!
- I told you to calm down! - Fight me!
- 진정하라고 했잖아! - 나와 싸워라!
Who is that?
그 사람은 누구입니까?
It's me.
나야.
What are you going to do about it?
그것에 대해 무엇을 할 건가요?
I've said this before, haven't I?
내가 전에도 이런 말을 한 적이 있지 않습니까?
(First one to swing is fined 5,000 Baht or fired)
(첫 번째 스윙 5,000바트의 벌금이 부과되거나 해고됨)
Speak up.
말하세요.
- "First one to swing is fined 5,000 Baht or fired."
- "먼저 스윙하는 사람에게는 5,000바트의 벌금이 부과되거나 해고됩니다."
Louder!
더 크게!
But Sky messed with Wayu first!
하지만 스카이가 먼저 와유를 망쳤어요!
Messed with him? Where's your proof?
그 사람을 엉망으로 만들었나요? 증거는 어디에 있나요?
I have my proof.
나는 증거를 가지고 있습니다.
Foei, I have a show tomorrow! What am I supposed to do?
포에이, 내일 공연이 있어요! 나는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
It hurts!
아파요!
Wayu. Tai.
와유. 타이.
To the black room.
검은 방으로.
Anything else you want to say to me?
나에게 또 하고 싶은 말은 없나요?
No, that's all.
아니, 그게 다야.
I must lock you.
나는 당신을 잠가야합니다.
Even if Sky was wrong for giving you that job.
스카이가 틀렸더라도 당신에게 그 일을 맡겨주셔서요.
In the end, Wayu, you accepted it.
결국 와유, 네가 받아들였구나.
You have to take responsibility for that choice.
책임을 져야 해 그 선택을 위해.
Understand?
이해하다?
Today,
오늘은
no one is getting fired.
아무도 해고되지 않습니다.
I'm not stupid enough to fire our second-best.
나는 충분히 바보가 아니다 우리의 차선책을 해고하기 위해.
- Thank you so much, Foei. - Thank you very much.
- 정말 고마워요, 포에이. - 매우 감사합니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
But I'm taking half a month of Tai's earnings
그런데 한달 반이 걸리네요 타이의 수입 중
to cover Sky's face treatment.
스카이의 페이스 트리트먼트를 커버하기 위해.
As for Wayu, you're suspended for three days
와유의 경우, 넌 3일 동안 정지됐어
until that wound on your head is healed.
네 머리의 상처가 나을 때까지.
Thank you, Foei.
고마워요, 포에이.
Tai.
타이.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
I dragged you into trouble.
내가 당신을 곤경에 빠뜨렸어요.
Hey, forget about it.
이봐, 잊어버려.
We're friends, man.
우린 친구야.
Friends should protect each other.
친구는 서로를 보호해야 합니다.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
You aren't in this alone.
당신은 혼자가 아닙니다.
Besides, I've wanted to punch that guy for a long time.
게다가 한 대 치고 싶었어 그 사람 오랜만이에요.
I don't care how much it costs me.
비용이 얼마나 드는지는 상관하지 않습니다.
Bad guy!
나쁜 놈!
Right on the chin!
바로 턱!
Honestly,
솔직히,
did my punch look good?
내 펀치 괜찮아 보였어?
Pretty good.
꽤 좋아요.
Boom! Upper-cut!
팔! 어퍼컷!
Hmph, what a shame.
흠, 정말 안타깝네요.
(Deleting work schedule for today, tomorrow, the day after)
(작업 일정 삭제 중 오늘, 내일, 모레)
Hello?
안녕하세요?
I'm actually free tonight. Can I work at your place?
사실 오늘 밤은 시간이 있어요. 내가 당신 집에서 일할 수 있나요?
Oh, I can just wait tables.
아, 그냥 테이블에서 기다릴 수도 있어요.
Perfect. I'll be there tomorrow at 6 PM.
완벽한. 내일 오후 6시에 거기에 갈게요.
Thank you so much. Thanks.
매우 감사합니다. 감사해요.
(Pay the utility bills, Go to work at Moonlit Last day of suspension of schooling)
(공과금 납부, 달빛에 출근 휴학 마지막 날)
Hey, is it done yet? The deadline is tomorrow!
아, 아직 끝나지 않았나요? 마감은 내일이에요!
All you do is sleep.
당신이 하는 일은 잠뿐이다.
Your mom is looking for you!
엄마가 널 찾고 있어!
- Let me sit. - Just sleep a bit.
- 앉게 해주세요. - 좀 자자.
- Sleep or work? - Fine, work.
- 잠을 잘까 아니면 일을 할까? - 알았어, 일해라.
How much is left?
얼마나 남았나요?
Quite a lot.
꽤 많이.
Here. Let me handle it.
여기. 제가 처리하겠습니다.
Good.
좋은.
(Post a building photo)
(건물 사진 게시)
Are you sure about withdrawing again? You're so close to graduating.
다시 탈퇴하시겠습니까? 졸업이 얼마 남지 않았네요.
Yes. I'm sure.
예. 나는 확신한다.
Alright. I'll need your documents, then.
괜찮은. 그럼 당신 서류가 필요해요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
You're welcome.
천만에요.
- Are you okay? - I'm fine. Bye.
- 괜찮으세요? - 잘 지내요. 안녕.
How is it, buddy?
어때요, 친구?
One-year membership.
1년 회원권.
- This is so fancy. - Haha.
- 정말 멋지네요. - 하하.
Right? I've got all problems cleared.
오른쪽? 모든 문제가 해결되었습니다.
- Come on! Get on! - I'm not so sure about this.
- 어서 해봐요! 타다! - 이건 잘 모르겠어요.
- Trust me, man! If you use this thing, - Right.
- 날 믿으세요! 이 물건을 사용하면, - 그렇죠.
you'll have the stamina to run back and forth to Pratunam over ten times!
넌 다시 달릴 수 있는 체력을 갖게 될 거야 그리고 프라투남까지 10번 이상!
Grip the handles tight.
손잡이를 꽉 잡으세요.
- Your legs! - Yeah.
- 다리! - 응.
There you go. Keep your legs tense!
됐어요. 다리를 긴장시키세요!
Tai.
타이.
Hmm?
흠?
I officially withdrew from my classes today.
공식적으로 탈퇴했어요 오늘 내 수업부터.
Yeah. Fine.
응. 괜찮은.
But don't give up, okay?
하지만 포기하지 마세요, 알았죠?
Just save up for now.
지금은 그냥 저축하세요.
Save up with me.
나와 함께 저장하십시오.
What are you saving up for anyway?
그런데 당신은 무엇을 위해 저축하고 있나요?
Getting married?
결혼?
Saving up for my car.
내 차를 위해 저축하세요.
My car needs new shock absorbers.
내 차에는 새로운 충격 흡수 장치가 필요합니다.
So that's why you're training this hard?
그래서 이렇게 열심히 훈련하는 거야?
Well, I have to go shirtless tonight. Since you're suspended,
음, 오늘 밤에는 셔츠를 벗고 나가야 해요. 정지되었으므로
it's my time to rake in the tips!
이제 팁을 긁어모을 시간이에요!
Ugh!
윽!
Are you training for the Olympics or something?
올림픽 준비 중이신가요? 아니면 뭔가?
Haha.
하하.
Stop! Don't distract me.
멈추다! 내 주의를 산만하게 하지 마세요.
Ugh.
윽.
Whatever you say.
당신이 무엇을 말하든.
I'm done.
난 끝났어.
I'm going to hit the sauna first.
먼저 사우나부터 가보겠습니다.
Go ahead.
계속하세요.
See you.
또 봐요.
Ah!
아!
Oh, Officer!
아, 경관님!
What a coincidence. Do you work out here, too?
정말 우연이군요. 여기서도 운동하시나요?
Yes.
예.
You too?
너도?
Well,
음,
something like that.
그런 것.
Excuse me?
실례합니다?
Yes?
예?
Could you help me apply some body oil?
바디 오일 바르는 것 좀 도와주실 수 있나요?
I'm not really available.
나는 정말로 시간이 없다.
Do you want to get arrested again?
또 체포되고 싶나요?
Arrested for what, Officer?
무슨 이유로 체포됐나요, 경관님?
Go ahead and arrest me, then.
그럼 저를 체포해 주세요.
By the way,
그런데,
what exactly would the charges be this time?
정확히 어떻게 될까요? 이번에는 요금이 청구되나요?
Or...
아니면...
Are you interested in my 'services'?
내 '서비스'에 관심이 있으신가요?
No.
아니요.
Well, if you ever change your mind,
글쎄요, 마음이 바뀌면
you can always find me at the club.
클럽에서는 언제나 나를 찾을 수 있어요.
Why are you looking at me like that?
왜 나를 그렇게 보는 거죠?
Hmm?
흠?
I haven't done anything wrong.
나는 아무 잘못도 하지 않았습니다.
Or...
아니면...
Do you want to check for yourself
직접 확인해 보시겠어요
to see if I'm hiding
내가 숨어 있는지 알아보려고
anything illegal?
불법적인 건 없나요?
See you around, Officer.
나중에 뵙겠습니다, 경관님.
Yes.
예.
Are you getting involved with that Soi 2 case?
당신은 에 참여하고 있습니까? 그 소이 2 케이스요?
It's a case I'm responsible for.
제가 책임져야 할 사건이에요.
You won't get promoted doing stuff like this.
당신은 승진할 수 없습니다 이런 짓을 하고 있습니다.
If you want to move up, listen to me.
위로 올라가고 싶다면 내 말을 들어보세요.
Take this case instead.
대신 이 사건을 맡아보세요.
I can't take on any more cases.
더 이상 사건을 맡을 수 없습니다.
Besides,
게다가,
the Soi 2 case
소이 2 사건
will lead to something much bigger.
훨씬 더 큰 일로 이어질 것입니다.
I'm seeing it through.
나는 그것을 끝까지 보고 있다.
- But you should... - I have a date with Rose.
- 하지만 해야 할 일은... - 로즈랑 데이트가 있어요.
If there's nothing else, I'll be going.
별 일 없으면 가겠습니다.
Fine, go.
좋아요, 가세요.
See you at home, Dad.
집에서 봐요, 아빠.
Well,
음,
this week,
이번 주
invite Rose for dinner.
로즈를 저녁 식사에 초대하세요.
I want to discuss important matters with her.
나는 토론하고 싶다 그녀와 중요한 문제.
Understood.
이해했다.
Sir, shall I serve the wine now?
선생님, 이제 와인을 드릴까요?
Not yet.
아직 아님.
Babe, I'm on my way. Wait for me.
자기야, 지금 가는 중이야. 기다려주세요.
I see.
알겠어요.
Should I order something for you?
제가 당신을 위해 뭔가를 주문해야 할까요?
No, it's okay. I just had some instant noodles.
아니요, 괜찮아요. 방금 라면을 먹었습니다.
Alright then.
그럼요.
Oh, Officer!
아, 경관님!
There you go again.
또 가네요.
Looking at me like a suspect.
나를 용의자처럼 바라보고 있다.
I came here to do a part-time job. I didn't come here to take on that kind of work.
저는 아르바이트를 하려고 여기에 왔습니다. 나는하지 않았다 그런 일을 맡으러 여기로 오세요.
I didn't say anything.
나는 아무 말도 하지 않았다.
I'm just here for dinner,
난 그냥 저녁 먹으러 왔어
not for an investigation.
수사를 위해서가 아닙니다.
Good to know.
알아두면 좋아요.
You're always staring at me.
당신은 항상 나를 쳐다보고 있습니다.
It's making me nervous.
그것은 나를 긴장하게 만든다.
Is something wrong? Or do you think I followed you here?
뭔가 문제가 있나요? 아니면 내가 당신을 따라 여기까지 왔다고 생각하시나요?
No. I was just lost in thought.
아뇨. 그냥 생각에 잠겨 있었을 뿐이에요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Wayu! Can you help with some foreign customers?
와유! 도와주실 수 있나요? 외국 고객들과 함께요?
Sure, I'm coming.
물론이죠. 갈 거예요.
Excuse me, Officer.
죄송합니다, 경관님.
I have to go back to my "honest work" now.
이제 나는 '정직한 일'로 돌아가야 한다.
Please, go ahead.
계속하세요.
(Rose: Something came up at home. I can't make it tonight)
(로즈: 집에 무슨 일이 생겼어요. 오늘 밤엔 못 갈 것 같아)
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
Check, please.
확인해주세요.
Hello, mind if I join you?
안녕하세요. 저도 함께해도 될까요?
Are you here alone?
여기 혼자 계시나요?
I was supposed to meet a friend.
친구를 만나기로 했어요.
She couldn't make it.
그녀는 그것을 할 수 없었다.
That's too bad.
안됐네요.
Want to go somewhere else?
다른 곳으로 가고 싶나요?
No, thanks. I'm heading home.
아니요, 고마워요. 나는 집으로 향하고 있다.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
My place is just around the corner.
내 집은 바로 모퉁이에 있습니다.
You'd better let me go.
나를 놓아주는 것이 좋을 것입니다.
I'm in a hurry.
나는 서둘러요.
Babe!
아기!
Babe, whose hand are you holding?
자기야, 누구 손을 잡고 있어?
Babe, are you cheating on me?
자기야, 너 나한테 바람피우는 거야?
He grabbed me first.
그 사람이 먼저 나를 잡았어요.
Babe, what does he have that I don't?
자기야, 그 사람이 갖고 있는데 나한테 없는 게 뭐야?
Answer me!
대답해주세요!
Are you calling me ugly?
나한테 못생겼다고 하는 거야?
I didn't say that!
나는 그렇게 말하지 않았다!
That's enough.
그것으로 충분합니다.
(Investigation)
(조사)
I'm a police officer.
저는 경찰관입니다.
If this turns into an assault, I will have to arrest you.
이게 폭행으로 변질되면 당신을 체포해야겠습니다.
Police?
경찰?
Okay, Officer!
좋아요, 경관님!
Check, please!
확인해주세요!
Are you hurt?
상처받았나요?
I'm fine.
잘 지내요.
Well...
음...
Do you have a change of clothes?
갈아입을 옷이 있나요?
No, but it's okay.
아니요, 하지만 괜찮아요.
Fine. I'll check the backroom. They might have something.
괜찮은. 뒷방을 확인해 보겠습니다. 그들에게 뭔가가 있을 수도 있습니다.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Officer.
장교.
It's fine.
괜찮습니다.
I just want to thank you
그저 감사하다는 말을 전하고 싶어요
for helping me back then.
그때 도와줘서.
Thank you very much.
매우 감사합니다.
Actually, just the fact that you'd lend me a jacket is plenty.
사실 그 사실만으로도 나에게 재킷을 빌려주면 충분하다.
Thank you very much indeed.
정말 감사합니다.
Don't mention it.
그것을 언급하지 마십시오.
Wayu, help with the serving!
와유, 서빙을 도와주세요!
Got it. I'm coming.
알았어요. 나는 간다.
Thanks. Well, I'll be going now.
감사해요. 글쎄요, 지금 가겠습니다.
See you then.
그럼 뵙겠습니다.
Oh, Officer!
아, 경관님!
You're still here?
아직 여기 있나요?
I was just finishing some work calls in the car.
막 마무리 중이었는데 차 안에서 업무 통화가 좀 있어요.
How are you getting home?
집에 어떻게 가나요?
I'll just catch a bus nearby.
그냥 근처에서 버스를 탈게요.
Aren't you afraid of getting attacked again?
두렵지 않나요? 또 공격당해?
Actually, I pass by your place.
사실 나는 당신이 있는 곳을 지나갑니다.
Want a ride?
차를 타고 싶나요?
Oh, would that be okay?
아, 괜찮을까요?
Well, thanks.
고마워요.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Okay. Drop me off right here.
좋아요. 나를 바로 여기에서 내려주세요.
Do you usually listen to this song?
평소 이 노래를 들어보시나요?
I'm just listening to the same songs on repeat, the same playlist.
같은 노래만 듣고 있어요 같은 재생목록이 반복됩니다.
Hmm.
흠.
Since you work these hours,
이 시간에 일을 하니까
who looks after your kid?
누가 네 아이를 돌봐주니?
Ah.
아.
He's just my nephew. I'm not that fast of a mover.
그는 단지 내 조카입니다. 나는 그렇게 빨리 움직이는 사람이 아니다.
And during the day?
그리고 낮에는?
Well,
음,
I drop him off at daycare.
나는 그를 어린이집에 데려다준다.
That's why I have to hustle for work.
그렇기 때문에 나는 서둘러 일을 해야 한다.
He's at that age where he's growing fast.
그는 빠르게 성장하고 있는 그 나이에 있다.
Doesn't your mom help?
엄마는 안 도와주시나요?
Well,
음,
she isn't really fond of childcare.
그녀는 육아를 별로 좋아하지 않는다.
So it means
그러니까
you're providing for the whole family on your own?
당신은 제공하고 온 가족이 혼자서?
Yeah.
응.
So I just have to keep hustling for gigs, taking whatever I can get. I need the cash.
그래서 계속 공연을 위해 분투해야 해요. 내가 얻을 수 있는 것은 무엇이든 가져가는 것. 현금이 필요해요.
You're impressive.
당신은 인상적입니다.
What was that?
그게 뭐였지?
I mean
내 말은
you're doing a great job.
당신은 훌륭한 일을 하고 있습니다.
Taking care of your family all by yourself like this.
가족을 돌보기 이렇게 혼자서.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
If you ever need help, let me know.
도움이 필요하면 알려주세요.
Just as long as it's nothing illegal.
불법이 아닌 한 말이죠.
Well, thanks for the ride.
글쎄, 태워줘서 고마워요.
I guess
아마
the taxes I paid are finally worth it today.
내가 낸 세금 오늘 마침내 그만한 가치가 있습니다.
This is my own gas money.
이것은 내 자신의 가스 돈입니다.
Not taxpayer money.
납세자의 돈이 아닙니다.
I was just kidding.
농담이에요.
Oh, I'll wash this jacket
아, 이 재킷은 세탁할게요
and return it to you.
그리고 그것을 당신에게 돌려주십시오.
It's fine.
괜찮습니다.
No, It's fine.
아니요, 괜찮아요.
I'll wash it until it smells great.
좋은 냄새가 날 때까지 세탁할게요.
And, once you're home, don't forget to let me know.
그리고 일단 집에 오면, 나에게 알려주는 것을 잊지 마세요.
Bye-bye!
안녕!
- Bye-bye. - Yes.
- 안녕. - 예.
Sigh.
한숨을 쉬다.
♪Just being the last one whom you think of♪
♪마지막이 되는 것 뿐이야 당신이 생각하는 사람♪
♪Standing where I never should have been♪
♪내가 절대로 있어서는 안 될 곳에 서 있었어♪
♪And honestly, that's enough for me♪
♪그리고 솔직히 저는 그것만으로도 충분해요♪
♪Just being the last one♪
♪마지막이 되는 것 뿐이야♪
♪Whom you look at♪
♪누구를 보고 있나요♪
♪To be in your cold gaze♪
♪차가운 시선 속에 있기를♪
♪Just this brings more happiness than I dreamed of♪
♪이것만으로도 더 행복해진다 내가 꿈꾸던 것보다 ♪
♪I'm just happy being right here♪
♪여기에 있어서 정말 기뻐요♪
Oh, no!
안 돼!
I forgot to ask for his Line ID.
나는 그의 라인 ID를 묻는 것을 잊었습니다.
Well.
잘.
(Wayu: Have you arrived home yet?)
(와유: 집에 아직 도착했어요?)
You have to thank your mom for getting his number.
엄마한테 감사해야 해 그의 전화번호를 알아내려고.
Yeah.
응.
Sorry, but can I bother you one last time? Can I borrow your phone? I need to call my mom.
미안하지만 마지막으로 귀찮게 해도 될까요? 전화기를 빌려도 될까요? 엄마에게 전화해야 해요.
Well,
음,
I sent him an SMS. Is he going to think I'm a creep?
나는 그에게 SMS를 보냈다. 그 사람은 내가 괴물이라고 생각할까?
I tried adding him on Line, but nothing popped up.
라인에 추가하려고 했는데, 하지만 아무것도 뜨지 않았습니다.
Don't sweat it.
너무 걱정하지 마세요.
Let's just see how he feels.
그가 어떻게 느끼는지 한번 볼까요?
Yeah, okay.
응, 알았어.
Wow.
우와.
(SMS, Krit: I'm home)
(SMS, Krit: 집에 왔어요)
Sigh.
한숨을 쉬다.
My cooking is unmatched.
내 요리는 타의 추종을 불허합니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
- Well, enjoy your meal. - Still as delicious as ever!
- 그럼, 맛있게 드세요. - 그래도 여전히 맛있어요!
Hmm.
흠.
It smells great.
냄새가 좋아요.
- Tai. - Hmm?
- 타이. - 흠?
Do you think this means like?
이것이 다음과 같은 뜻이라고 생각하시나요?
Who? Him or you?
WHO? 그 사람인가요 아니면 당신인가요?
Him, obviously!
그 사람은 분명히!
I mean, there's a chance.
내 말은, 기회가 있다는 거야.
But first,
하지만 먼저
you need to check if he has a partner.
그 사람에게 파트너가 있는지 확인해야합니다.
Wow, look at you being a "good guy."
와, 당신이 "좋은 사람"인 것 좀 보세요.
It's not about being good. It's about strategy.
잘 되라는 것이 아닙니다. 전략에 관한 것입니다.
If he has one, we'll know if he's worth stealing!
그에게 하나가 있다면, 그 사람을 훔칠 가치가 있는지 우리가 알게 될 거예요!
Wow, you!
와, 너!
Sigh.
한숨을 쉬다.
Look.
바라보다.
Just ask him out again.
그에게 다시 한번 데이트 신청을 해보세요.
Prove it one way or another.
어떤 식으로든 증명해 보세요.
Otherwise,
그렇지 않으면
you'll just keep overthinking like this.
계속 이렇게 지나치게 생각하게 될 거예요.
Right?
오른쪽?
You want me
당신은 나를 원해요
to text him?
그에게 문자 보내려고?
No. Just go to the Investigation Department
아니요. 그냥 가세요 수사부
or the station.
아니면 역.
You've got to make your move in person.
직접 움직여야 합니다.
Is our Wayu finally going to be "off the market"?
우리 와유가 드디어 되는 걸까 "시장 밖에서"?
Hey! It's nothing like that.
여기요! 그런 것이 아닙니다.
It's just a cop hitting on him.
그냥 경찰이 그 사람을 때리는 것뿐이에요.
- Wow. - Yeah.
- 우와. - 응.
Let me give you some advice.
몇 가지 조언을 드리겠습니다.
Listen.
듣다.
Cops aren't all that great. Don't lose your heart to them.
경찰은 그다지 훌륭하지 않습니다. 그들에게 마음을 잃지 마십시오.
The girls in Soi 2 have suffered enough.
소이2의 소녀들은 충분히 고통받았습니다.
Stay single like this. It's better.
이렇게 싱글로 지내세요. 더 좋습니다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
It's all about the strategy. Trust me.
그것은 전략에 관한 것입니다. 나를 믿으세요.
There are plenty of good cops out there.
세상에는 좋은 경찰이 많이 있습니다.
Hang on a sec.
잠깐만요.
- Oh, my! - What?
- 아, 이런! - 무엇?
Pitak.
피탁.
- Good to see you. - Oh, hello.
- 만나서 반가워요. - 아, 안녕하세요.
- Hello.
- 안녕하세요.
How are you?
어떻게 지내세요?
- How have you been? - Same as usual.
- 잘 지냈어요? - 평소와 똑같습니다.
Still busy as ever.
여전히 여전히 바쁘다.
But if Krit can follow in my footsteps, I'll have nothing left to worry about.
하지만 크리트가 내 발자취를 따라갈 수 있다면, 걱정할 게 하나도 남지 않을 거예요.
Hehe.
헤헤.
So, what about the wedding between our kids?
그렇다면 결혼식은 어떨까? 우리 아이들 사이에?
They've been together forever.
그들은 영원히 함께했습니다.
- Yeah. - But they haven't tied the knot yet.
- 응. - 하지만 아직 매듭을 묶지 않았어요.
People are starting to gossip that Krit doesn't like women.
사람들이 험담을 하기 시작해요 Krit은 여자를 좋아하지 않는다고요.
Hmm.
흠.
Maybe we should let her answer that herself.
아마도 우리는 그래야 할 것입니다 그녀가 스스로 대답하게 해주세요.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
- Hello.
- 안녕하세요.
What were you all discussing?
다들 무슨 얘기를 하고 있었나요?
We were talking about the wedding!
우리는 결혼식에 대해 이야기하고 있었어요!
Oh.
오.
You say it.
당신은 그것을 말한다.
Please don't pressure Krit. I'm not ready yet either.
Krit에게 압력을 가하지 마세요. 나도 아직 준비가 안 됐어요.
My business is still growing.
내 사업은 여전히 ​​​​성장하고 있습니다.
Krit said he's willing to wait for me.
Krit는 나를 기꺼이 기다릴 의향이 있다고 말했습니다.
We'd like to see it happen soon.
우리는 그것이 곧 일어나는 것을 보고 싶습니다.
Mm-hmm.
음-흠.
When is it going to be?
언제쯤 될까요?
Darn it! He already has a girlfriend?
젠장! 그 사람은 이미 여자친구가 있어요?
Hey, Wayu!
안녕, 와유!
Hmm?
흠?
But I only do it with my boyfriend.
그런데 저는 남자친구랑만 해요.
That's not a problem.
그건 문제가 되지 않습니다.
(Only available on WeTV, Every Friday, 8 PM)
(WeTV에서만 시청 가능하며, 매주 금요일 오후 8시)
♪I love you with all my heart, and I'm ready to give you everything♪
♪ 진심으로 당신을 사랑합니다. 그리고 나는 당신에게 모든 것을 줄 준비가 되어있습니다♪
♪Everything a person has in life♪
♪사람이 인생에서 가지고 있는 모든 것♪
♪I won't run away from you, no matter what we face♪
♪나는 당신에게서 도망치지 않을 거예요 무슨 일이 있어도♪
♪No matter how bad it gets♪
♪아무리 상황이 나빠져도 상관없어♪
♪I give you my whole self, my everything♪
♪나의 모든 것, 나의 모든 것을 당신에게 드립니다♪
♪Please trust your life with someone like me♪
♪당신의 인생을 믿어주세요 나같은 사람이랑♪
♪Be sure that no one♪
♪아무도 없도록 하세요♪
♪Could ever love you more than I do♪
♪언제든지 나보다 당신을 더 사랑할 수 있을 거에요♪
♪Like a poem, heartache♪
♪시처럼 마음이 아프다♪
♪Won't stay with us for long, but will slowly fade away♪
♪우리와 오래 머물지 않을 거예요. 하지만 천천히 사라질 거예요♪
♪You came into my life and carried me away♪
♪당신은 내 삶에 들어왔습니다 날 데려가줬어♪
♪To something I never expected♪
♪예상도 못한 일에♪
♪To truly understand a love beyond reason♪
♪진정으로 이해하려면 이유를 초월하는 사랑♪
♪When I found someone like you♪
♪당신 같은 사람을 찾았을 때♪
♪My whole life no longer has to keep dreaming♪
♪내 인생은 더 이상 계속 꿈을 꾸어야 해요♪
♪Now that you're right here♪
♪이제 여기 오셨네요♪
♪I love you with all my heart, and I'm ready to give you everything♪
♪ 진심으로 당신을 사랑합니다. 그리고 나는 당신에게 모든 것을 줄 준비가 되어있습니다♪
♪Everything a person has in life♪
♪사람이 인생에서 가지고 있는 모든 것♪
♪I won't run away from you, no matter what we face♪
♪나는 당신에게서 도망치지 않을 거예요 무슨 일이 있어도♪
♪No matter how bad it gets♪
♪아무리 나빠도 상관없어♪
♪I give you my whole self, my everything♪
♪나의 모든 것, 나의 모든 것을 당신에게 드립니다♪
♪Please trust your life with someone like me♪
♪당신의 인생을 믿어주세요 나같은 사람이랑♪
♪Be sure that no one♪
♪아무도 없도록 하세요♪
♪Could ever love you more than I do♪
♪언제든지 나보다 당신을 더 사랑할 수 있을 거에요♪
♪Whoa oh oh♪
♪워오오오♪
♪Oh baby♪
♪오 자기야♪
♪To truly understand a love beyond reason♪
♪진정으로 이해하려면 이유를 초월하는 사랑♪
♪When I found someone like you♪
♪당신 같은 사람을 찾았을 때♪
♪My whole life no longer has to keep dreaming♪
♪내 인생은 더 이상 계속 꿈을 꾸어야 해요♪
♪Now that you're right here♪
♪이제 여기 오셨네요♪
♪I love you with all my heart, and I'm ready to give you everything♪
♪ 진심으로 당신을 사랑합니다. 그리고 나는 당신에게 모든 것을 줄 준비가 되어있습니다♪
♪Everything a person has in life♪
♪사람이 인생에서 가지고 있는 모든 것♪
♪I won't run away from you, no matter what we face♪
♪나는 당신에게서 도망치지 않을 거예요 무슨 일이 있어도♪
♪No matter how bad it gets♪
♪아무리 상황이 나빠져도 상관없어♪
♪I give you my whole self, my everything♪
♪나의 모든 것, 나의 모든 것을 당신에게 드립니다♪
♪Please trust your life with someone like me♪
♪당신의 인생을 믿어주세요 나같은 사람이랑♪
♪Be sure that no one♪
♪아무도 없도록 하세요♪
♪Could ever love you more than I do♪
♪언제든지 나보다 당신을 더 사랑할 수 있을 거에요♪
♪No one♪
♪아무도 없어요♪